<view>
    <title>Moss Settings</title>
    <description>You will find all the settings related to Moss here.</description>

    <subtitle>Moss options</subtitle>

    <toggle key="allow_statistics">Allow statistics</toggle>
    <subtext>
        This allows tracking usage statistics.
        As of currently this data is not shared but may be accessed by extensions.
    </subtext>

    <toggle key="portable_mode">Portable mode</toggle>
    <subtext>
        This disables the installer screen on startup and
        allows you to run from an extracted folder without installing.
    </subtext>

    <subtitle>Sync options</subtitle>

    <toggle key="wait_for_everything_to_load">Wait for everything to load</toggle>
    <subtext>
        This forces all the documents to be ready before opening the main menu.
        This may lead to increased load times, depending on the size of your cloud.
    </subtext>

    <toggle key="download_everything">Download everything</toggle>
    <subtext fore="defaults:RED">THIS IS AN EXPERIMENTAL FEATURE</subtext>
    <subtext>
        This option downloads any documents that are visible in the main menu and were not downloaded before.
    </subtext>

    <toggle key="download_last_opened_page_to_make_preview">Download last page to make preview</toggle>
    <subtext>
        This feature downloads only the necessary data to create a preview thumbnail of the document,
        without having to open it.
    </subtext>

    <toggle key="save_last_opened_folder">Save last opened folder</toggle>
    <subtext>
        Enabling this will maintain the currently opened folder,
        every time you open the app. If you disable this it will maintain whichever folder it last saved.
        The default folder is "My Files".
    </subtext>

    <toggle key="save_after_close">Save after closing a document</toggle>
    <subtext fore="defaults:ORANGE">This feature may be unstable!</subtext>
    <subtext>
        This option causes the document to be uploaded after closing the document viewer.
        This will update data such as the current page or last opened.
    </subtext>

    <subtitle>UI options</subtitle>

    <toggle key="enable_fake_screen_refresh">Enable fake screen refresh</toggle>
    <subtext>
        This is a deprecated feature,
        where some UI interactions cause the screen to do a fake eink refresh.
        This feature may be disturbing to some users or otherwise annoying.
    </subtext>

    <toggle key="maintain_aspect_size">Maintain aspect size</toggle>
    <subtext>
        This will keep documents loaded in the document viewer sized to the original window size.
        If you disable this, the page size will instead try to scale to whatever window size you have instead,
        if you resized the window.
    </subtext>

</view>